bigxgh.com 2016-05-09

# BiGx.Com.Gh

BiGxGh.Com™ takes your privacy seriously. This notice explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. This notice is available on our homepage.

* * *

##### **What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This policy covers how BiGxGh treats personal information that BiGxGh collects and receives, including information related to your past use of BiGxGh products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that BiGxGh does not own or control, or to people that BiGxGh does not employ or manage. In addition, certain BiGxGh associated companies have their own privacy statements.

* * *

##### **Information Collection and Use General  **

BiGxGh collects personal information when you register with BiGxGh, when you use BiGxGh products or services, when you visit BiGxGh pages or the pages of certain BiGxGh partners. BiGxGh may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with BiGxGh and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. BiGxGh collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of products and services that we offer. BiGxGh automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, BiGxGh cookie information, and the page you request. BiGxGh uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

* * *

##### **Children  **

BiGxGh does not allow a child under age 13 to register for any BiGxGh services. BiGxGh does not ask a child under age 13 for any personal information.

* * *

##### **Information Sharing and Disclosure  **

BiGxGh does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with BiGxGh under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help BiGxGh communicate with you about offers from BiGxGh and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of BiGxGh’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. We transfer information about you if BiGxGh is acquired by or merged with another company.

In this event, BiGxGh will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. BiGxGh displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria – for example, men ages 16-24 from a particular geographic area. BiGxGh does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. BiGxGh works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business.

* * *

##### **Cookies  **

BiGxGh may set and access BiGxGh cookies on your computer. BiGxGh lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to BiGxGh’s cookies. BiGxGh uses web beacons to access BiGxGh cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with BiGxGh products and services.

* * *

##### **Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences  **

You can edit your BiGxGh Account Information, at any time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the BiGxGh service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the BiGxGh Newsletter, that are considered part of your BiGxGh account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. You can delete your BiGxGh account by visiting our Account Deletion page. Please click here to read about information that might possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted.

* * *

##### **Confidentiality and Security  **

BiGxGh limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

* * *

##### **Changes to this Privacy Policy  **

BiGxGh may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your BiGxGh account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

Effective Date: April 22, 2014.
